rombus-group.com 2019-07-11

# PRIVACY POLICY

PRIVACY POLICY “Rombus Group LLC” pledges to protect your confidential information. The privacy
policy clarifies what information we collect about you, how we use the information we collect about you,
how you can tell us if you choose to restrict the use of such information.
 By submitting your information, you consent to the use of such information in accordance with this
privacy policy. If we change our privacy policy, any changes will be posted on this page without prior
notice.
 WHAT IS YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU? We collect information about users
of our website in several ways, including using identification files that are stored in the client system,
through registration, as well as through e-mail messages sent to us through our website. The information
collected includes the following: if you send us an email, you automatically give us your email address and
other personal information included in the text of your message.
 If you call our technical support center, or leave a voice message, you agree to give us your name, contact
number(s), your email address, and any other personal data that you agree to provide to our technical
specialists with so that our technical experts can respond to your request.
 We collect and store information from all visitors to our website, which they either actively make
available to us, or during their simple browsing of our website: computer address on the network (IP),
browser type, operating system type, date and the time of access to our website, the address of the
Internet resource from which the user was redirected to our website. We use this information to track
the traffic to our website, count the number of visitors in different sections of the website, and also to
make our website more useful.
 WHAT DO WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT? We use personal data in order to provide
you with the services that you give us ask you to provide. Unless you notify us that you no longer wish
to receive this kind of information, we may periodically inform you about our products and services. By
telling us your personal data via e-mail or telephone, you agree to our use of your information in the
manner described in this clause.
 We can conduct statistical analyzes of user behavior (for example, analyzing data on the use of the
website, passively from all users) in order to determine the relative degree of consumer interest in various
sections of our website. Such an analysis will help us in our efforts to further improve the product.
 WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE THE COLLECTED INFORMATION? We will provide your personal data if
required by law, including, at the request of the courts, by order of the court, when called to the courts
as a witness, or in accordance with other requirements of federal, regional or municipal laws.
 We may transfer statistical data to third parties in summary form without disclosing any personal data to
our users.
 HOW CAN YOU REFUSE FROM INFORMATION FROM US? If you do not want us to contact you about our
products or services, you can let us know either at the time you provide us with your contact information,
or at any other time by sending an email to info@rombus-group.com
 WHAT MEANS OF PROTECTION ARE APPLIED TO PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION? All information relating
to you, stored on our web server, is placed in closed databases and protected by a number of technical
means of access control.
